http://www.chefreco.com/terms_privacy.asp

Charbroilers, Griddles, Hot Plates
Coffee, Tea Brewers, Grinders, Etc.
Concession, Hot Dog, Popcorn etc.
Food Preparation
Food Grinders, Choppers, Peelers, etc.
Flatware Savers, Retrievers
Floor Care - Mop, Sweep, Etc.
Hand Dryers
Matting - Anti Fatigue, Drainage, Entryway, etc.
Colanders
Cutlery, Turners, Etc.
Cutting Boards, Butcher Blocks
Dispensers, Kitchen
Food Safety
Fry Pans, Covers
Gloves, Mitts (NOT disposable)
Misc Refrigeration
Pizza Prep.
Warewashing
Glass Washers, Glass Racks etc.
Dish Racks, Dollies
Disposals, Disposers, Waste Drains
Faucets, Assemblies
Flatware Washing, Storage
Glass Washers, Racks etc.
Charbroilers, Griddles, Hot Plates
Coffee, Tea Brewers, Grinders, Etc.
Concession, Hot Dog, Popcorn etc.
Food Preparation
Food Grinders, Choppers, Peelers, etc.
Flatware Savers, Retrievers
Floor Care - Mop, Sweep, Etc.
Hand Dryers
Matting - Anti Fatigue, Drainage, Entryway, etc.
Colanders
Cutlery, Turners, Etc.
Cutting Boards, Butcher Blocks
Dispensers, Kitchen
Food Safety
Fry Pans, Covers
Gloves, Mitts (NOT disposable)
Misc Refrigeration
Pizza Prep.
Warewashing
Glass Washers, Glass Racks etc.
Dish Racks, Dollies
Disposals, Disposers, Waste Drains
Faucets, Assemblies
Flatware Washing, Storage
Glass Washers, Racks etc.
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
The information we gather online from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Chefreco.com. Here are the types of information we gather.
When ordering or registering, we receive and store any information (including name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information) you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. We DO NOT store credit card information. You can choose not to provide certain information, but this can limit your access to many of our features. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors, and visits, to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
How do we use your information?
Information about our customers is an important part
of our business, and we are NOT in the business of selling it to others.
We work in conjunction with other companies and individuals to perform
functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling, shipping and delivering
orders, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They
have access to address information needed to perform their functions, but may
not use it for other purposes.
We release account and other personal information when we believe release is
appropriate to comply with the law or protect the rights, property, or safety
of Chefreco.com, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information
with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk
reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing,
or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for
commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy
Notice.
How do we protect visitor information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the
safety of your personal information. All sensitive/credit information you
supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then
encrypted into our databases.
We reveal only the last four digits of your credit card numbers when confirming
an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the
appropriate credit card company during order processing.
It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password
and to your computer. Be sure to sign off and close your browser window when
finished using a shared computer.
Do we use "cookies"?
Chefreco uses “cookies” to improve our customer’s shopping
experience. The cookie itself does not contain personal information although it
will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have
specifically and knowingly provided.
We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better
understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to
use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and
improve our business.
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent,
or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser
settings. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that
make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not
function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by
contacting customer service.
Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include Restaurant Equipment Co. of Savannah, Inc. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?
To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by
modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section. Please note
that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in
production. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, but are
receiving them, please contact customer service to be removed.
To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into
the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping
addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may
maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service
that transaction and for record keeping.
Third party links
In an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third
party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent
privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the
content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect
the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites
(including if a specific link does not work).
Protecting Children's
Privacy
Chefreco.com adheres to a strict privacy code regarding children
and does not knowingly accept personal information from any child under the age
of 13. If it is brought to our attention that we have inadvertently received
personal information from a child under 13, we will immediately remove all
personal and identifiable information from our records in compliance with the
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998. In addition, we will not
disclose this information to any other companies.
Changes to our policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on June
2015.
Terms and Conditions
Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.
Your consent
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
